Lloyd: So now that you're finished
session one of unit three, it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
You can access the assessment by clicking
on the assessment link on page three
and downloading and saving that in a
suitable location on your computer.
Once you've done that, you can
open the assessment booklet and
begin with assessment three.
I would also strongly recommend
downloading the hints and tips, which will
assist you in completing the questions.
So as with the other two assessments,
you have the assessment guidance
at the top and then on page two, if
you pop your name at the top, you
come to section one: Understand Key
Legislation Related to Cyber Security.
There is only one learning outcome in
section one, so there's only one question.
And this one is asking you in the
table below, provide a summary
of three key points of current
legislation related to cyber security
which is the designed to protect
individuals, businesses, and nations.
So give three key points for
legslation that will protect
individuals, businesses, and nations.
And it's asking for a summary there.
Once you've done that, you can
then save the assessment booklet
and move on to section two.